There are real life dragon slayers? Yeah.
There are evil beasts out there that do
bad things to people called devil dragons.
This one mighty and
brave adventurer slayed
one of those dragons by
cutting off his head.
Then the scales, claws, fangs,
and bones of the creature.
They were used to create high
quality weapons and medicine.
It brought great wealth
to the countryside.
Wow.
After that, the brave and
mighty adventurer was a hero,
who the people called the Dragon Slayer.
I want to be one!
I want to be a Dragon Slayer!
That's no easy task.
Some dragons are incredibly tough and fierce,
and have lived for thousands of years.
They can make the ground
tremble just by walking,
and even crumble mountains
with a swat of their tail.
In fact, long ago this continent was almost
destroyed by the dragons running wild.
They'd chomp on little kids
like you for a snack huh?
What's
that
over there huh?
Is it trouble I don't know but I
have this crazy feeling something's
out there Ahead of us I don't see
anything you don't it's right there
How can this be a dragon of calamity?
Ah…
I don't know how to take
off my feelings I don't
know what I can achieve I
want to find what I want
I don't want to touch
I'll go back to the end
I can't wait to see the number I want to.
I can't wait to see the
light that has a change.
I'm not too old.
I can't wait to see the light.
I don't believe it.
Does the Empire not understand
the terror they have unleashed?
Our records state that it's only been 150
years since the beast
fell into hibernation.
It should be in its dormant
period right now. The fools!
What are they doing?
Who resorts to using something so
devastating over a simple dispute?
Quickly now,
round up everyone who took shelter in the
capital and have them
evacuate immediately?
Everyone yes sir, if they try to stay,
carry them out, if they cling
to their belongings, drag them.
Leave not a single person in the capital!
I'm sensing that obstruction
magic is being used.
It's blocking the exits.
It'll be impossible now.
The Sovereign Six won't be able to unite.
Damn these wretched nuisances!
Majesty!
You must leave now!
When that thing gets here,
we won't stand a chance!
I need you warriors to protect the people.
Focus on guiding them
away from the capital
and take refuge wherever you can find it.
I still have my own responsibilities
right here in the capital.
In the path of that dragon,
there is no doubt the capital
will be thoroughly destroyed.
Right now, they should
be evacuating everyone.
If so, then,
my father, he'll surely choose to stay
behind and use himself as a shield.
But then...
I know.
Even someone as strong as him is
no match for something like that.
Please, father.
You must leave.
A dragon, huh?
Wow, they're even bigger than I thought.
This is the first one
I've ever seen in person.
What?
You sure about that?
He just defeated a Black Death dragon.
Hey, Lin, do you happen to know if your
brother and father are still in the city?
Yes.
I have no doubt they've stayed behind.
But it's too late for us to help them.
No, I think I can do it.
If I run.
If you run?
Look how far away we are.
Yeah.
Remember what we did against the goblin?
I think we could do that here.
You mean the wind blast we used?
Yeah, I suppose that would be one option.
But it's going to hit you pretty hard.
The sword will take the brunt of it.
Let me help out.
I owe a lot to your dad
and the people of the city.
And I want to lend them a hand if I can.
Getting him out shouldn't be too hard.
Surely I can handle that much at least.
Okay.
I guess so.
Stop it, Lin.
Why am I sitting here being pessimistic?
He's my teacher.
And he says he can handle it.
Now, Windblast is not normally
a spell that's used on people.
But this is one person who I should
not try to compare with anybody normal.
There's no need to hesitate.
That's what you're telling me, right?
Huh?
Foolish of you, King Clays.
Crushing your meager country into
submission is a simple task for me.
No matter the extent of your threats,
I cannot and will not hand the
Dungeon of the Lost over to you.
Your idle hands are letting
such great power go to waste.
Combined with the
intelligence of my empire,
it could be a military force strong
enough to control the known world.
We merely chose not to use a power
that's beyond what we can control.
Surely you can understand the
repercussions of such a thing?
Then that is precisely why you will
forever be a king of insignificance.
As long as I've known you, you have
never had the starch in you to rule.
There's nothing else that he cares about.
He only wants to get his hands
on what's in that dungeon.
I underestimated him.
I never expected he would throw the
full force of his might like this.
Letting negotiations break
down was a mistake on my part.
Good father!
The capital faces certain doom, and
all I can think about is my daughter.
Some leader I am.
Never had it in me to be king.
He's exactly right.
I know who I am.
I've always been more
suited for the battlefield.
I'm truly sorry to the people of this fine
country who have blindly
obeyed their foolish king.
It won't be enough to make amends
for my sins, but at the very least,
I'm going to take one of
its damn eyes with me!
Summon Divine Shield!
Sir Noor, stand in front of this cylinder.
Oh, okay.
Magic Barrier.
Reflect!
Magic Reflect!
Enhance!
What's that?
Charge!
Burst!
It seems different from
the last time we did this.
Condense!
Right, here we go.
The impact!
It'll be much more intense than last time.
Apologies in advance.
Hold on, I...
Multicast!
Okay, I've put everything
that I have into this.
Six-ball cast!
Windblast Force!
Kei-sensei.
Godspeed.
Is that the same Elder
Dragon who just several
hundred years ago burned down the realm?
Hmm.
It's not going to give me
the chance to retaliate.
Well, I must do something kingly at least.
A grand finale.
Come!
Come get me!
Allow me to show you how resolute we are!
The Blasting Sword.
It channels all the wielder's
sacrificial mana into one final blow.
So he's sacrificing himself.
Do it!
Covered in a cloud of dust
because of this little
person the strong control
the weak and crush
them with violence that
is the natural law of
this world and any who
dare oppose it shall fall?
Oh, that's what I'm going to do!
Harry!
Ah!
I thought I was just about to die.
Six-Bull Cast!
Wind Blast Force!
Physical enhancement!
Man, that was a close one.
Oh, crap, the walls!
Oh, the dragon!
It was so far away just a second ago.
Oh, God!
I can't stop myself!
I'm gonna smash into it!
Parry!
Well, I made it in one piece.
But I'm gonna tell Lin we're
never doing that again.
Anyways, that was easier
to parry than I expected.
It's a shock how huge
this dragon actually is.
The impact from Lin's magic
really threw me for a loop.
So really, this doesn't
seem all that scary.
Right now, I think I might
be able to fight this thing.
I can't believe all the damage. Right?
Okay then,
the two of us will find the
king and get him out of here,
while Sir Noor fights the Elder Dragon.
Watch out, above you!
Lady Lindbergh!
Thank you.
You just saved my life.
Lady Lindbergh, I need
you to stay close to me.
Goblin!
Emperors!
Comparatively, they're quite small
to the one Noor and I confronted.
But they're still Goblin Emperors, and
they are monsters in a league of their own.
How should we fight them?
I need to start thinking
like Instructor Noor does.
What would he say?
Listen to me.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Our fight is with some mere Goblins.
Yes, you're right.
Compared to that dragon, this is
something we can easily handle.
Let's keep our cool and take care of this.
Now, ice dance!
Fast!
They still stand down.
Don't move.
I stopped moving!
How he does!
Divine sword!
That's a nest for you.
Not only do people call
her the Divine Shield,
but she's more than worthy of
her Divine Sword, Title II.
And while Rolo...
I saw him stop those huge
goblins with just a few words.
Demon folk are a marvel.
So much power within such a young boy.
It must take a great deal of courage
to wield something like that.
Let's get moving!
This makes no sense.
Harry!
I don't understand.
My claws and scales are indestructible.
How is this happening?
I swear this thing never gets a single
scratch, no matter what hits it.
Seriously, what is the
deal with this sword?
Either way, it is the key to victory.
I might finish this.
I'll use my attack.
That has never failed me.
Harry!
He just parried the dragon's breath.
Instructor!
It's angry. Huh?
But it's more than that.
The dragon's frustrated because Noor
isn't treating it as a serious threat.
It's not used to being so disregarded.
Dragons are very prideful beasts.
Especially the Elder Dragon, which
believes it is more powerful than anything.
But in watching this fight,
it's almost as though...
The one who is weak.
The one who is small.
This time is me.
Mary.
It seems like it's calmed
down, what's happening?
I am.
I think it's actually submitting to him.
What is going on right now?
Wow, look at that.
Then the scales, claws,
fangs, and bones of the creature,
they were used to create
high-quality weapons and medicine.
It brought great wealth
to the countryside.
After that,
the brave and mighty adventurer was a hero
Who the people called the Dragon Slayer.
Oh, come on.
I don't think I'm exactly hero material.
It doesn't want to fight anymore.
Instructor Noor!
Instructor!
Thank
you
so
much
for
watching.
I don't have to die on this side.
Don't give up your heart.
If you give up your heart,
it's not the same way.
Don't let you go, don't let you go.
Don't let you go, don't let me go.
Take a shot, clap, clap.
See you
next
time.